Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Government business and correspondence, 1982-1990; Series 2
  - Legislation, 1982-1990; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - DC Family and Medical Leave Act, 1990; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - DC Health Occupations Revisions Act of 1989, Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - DC Health Occupation Revisions Act, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - DC Human Rights Act, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - DC Laws Effective May 10, 1988, Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - DC Prison Legislation, 1989; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - DC Regional Interstate Banking Act of 1985, Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - DC Right to Family Leave Bill 7-57, 1987; Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - DC Taxicab Establishment Act of 1985, Series 2, subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Employee Motor Vehicle Act, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Enrolled Legislation, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Estate Tax Legislation '86, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Franchising Act, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Gun Legislation, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Homelessness Legislation, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Housing/Legislation, 1985-1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Imitations Pistols '86, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Initiative 28 (Bottle Bill), 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Initiative Measure 28, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Interference with Medical Health Care Facilities Act of 1989, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Land Use Element of the Comprehensive Plan, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Legislation, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Legislation Introduced by Councilman Winter, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Efforts/Lobbying, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Loitering/Vagrancy Laws, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Lottery Unclaimed Prizes Student Activities Allocation Amendment Act, 1985-1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - McBride Principle, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Motor Vehicle Driving Amendments Act of 1985, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Municipal Integrity Act of 1987, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Municipal Integrity, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Prescription Drug Price Information Act, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Procurement Practices Act, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Prohibition of Horse Drawn Carriages Trade Act, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Prompt Pay, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Closing Dead End Alley on the Northwest, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Public Assistance of 1982, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - NPW Personal Bills 1989, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Religious Leave Bill, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Resolutions, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Resolutions, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Right to Pregnancy Leave Act, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Smoking Regulation Act of 1990, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Tree Preservation Act of 1989, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - The Washington Post, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with government or public agencies of the District of Columbia, 1985-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Anacostia Senior High School, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong High School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Ballou High School, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Anne Beers Elementary School, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Blow Elementary School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Bryan Elementary School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Parking Services, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Capitol Hill Traffic Management Task Force - Minutes, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Chief Maurice Turner, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Consortium of Universities, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Correctional Treatment Facility [1/3], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Correctional Treatment Facility [2/3], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Correctional Treatment Facility [3/3], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence to Schools, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Department of Corrections, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Department of Corrections, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Department of Employee Services, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Department of Finance and Revenue, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Department of Human Services, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Human Services - Candace Black, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Department of Human Services Control Referral Bureau, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Department of Human Rights and Minority Business Development, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Department of Public and Assited Housing, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Department of Public Works - Annual Report, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Department of Public Works - Contracts, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Department of Recreation and Parks, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - DC Agencies Space Rental Data, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - DC Armory Board, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - DC Department of Human Services, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - DC DS List, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - DC Energy Office, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - The District of Columbia Office of Documents, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - DC Prison, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - DC Prison, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - DC Prison [1/2], 1986-1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - DC Prison [2/2], 1986-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - DC Public Library, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - DC Law School [1/3], 1987-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - DC Law School [2/3], 1987-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - DC Law School [3/3], 1987-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - DC Public Library, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - DC Public Schools, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - DC Public Schools [1/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - DC Public Schools [2/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - DC School of Law, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - DC State Health Planning and Development Agency, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Department of Administrative Services, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Department of Correction Halfway, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Public Works [1/2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Public Works [2/2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Department of Public Works, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Department of Public Works FY 1989 Council Budget Hearing - Follow-up Questions, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Senior High School, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Elliot Junior High School Parent/Student Roster, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Fire Department, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Fraternal Order of Police, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Goding Elementary School, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Hine Junior High School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Judiciary Square Detention Facility, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Ketchum Elementary School, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - ketcham Elementary School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Kingsman Elementary School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Ludlow-Taylor Elementary School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Marie Reed Community School, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Maury Elementary School, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Mayor's Proposed Prison Site Resolution, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - McKinley High School, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Metro, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Metro Bus-Potomac Ave., 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Metro Green Line, 1988-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Metro Task Force Survey Questionaire, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Metro Transit Info, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Metropolitan Committee on Aids Issues, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Metropolitan Police Department, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Miner Elementary School, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Lucy Ellen Moten Elementary School, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Neighborhood Planning for Stuart Junior High and Julius Hobson Middle Schools, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - National Museum on American History, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - News from the District of Columbia Taxicab Commission, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Administrator, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Office on Aging, 1987-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Office on Aging - Some, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Office of Banking and Financial Institutions, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Office of Business and Economics Development, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - OBED Annual Report, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Office of Cable Television [1/2], 1986-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Office of Cable Television [2/2], 1986-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Office of Campaign Finance, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Office of the Comptroller of the Currency, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Office of Coordination for Community Based Residential Facilities, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Office of the Corporation Counsel, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Office of Criminal Justice Plans and Analysis, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Office of the District of Columbia Auditor, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Office of Early Childhood Development, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Office of Human Rights, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Office of Intergovermental Relations, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Office of Motion Picture and TV Development, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Office of the People's Counsel - DC, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Office of Personnel, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Orr Elementary School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - PACT Program, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Parhem Permit, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - People's Councel Nomination, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Pepco [1/2], 1988-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Pepco [2/2], 1988-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Pepco, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Plummer Elementary School, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Police Budget, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Police Reserves, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Prison, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Prison Site Resolution, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Proposed Stadium/Armory, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Public Schools, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Public School - Special Education, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Public Vehicle Services, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Recorder of Deeds, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Roberson, F. Alexis H., 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Ross School Parent Teacher Association, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - School Closings, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Self Sufficiency Activities, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Sinderbrand, Paul, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Hispanic Heritage, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Smithsonian Institution - Anacostia Museum, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - State Health Planning and Development Agency, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Stuart Junior High School, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Superintendent - DC Public Schools, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Takoma Metro Station, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Taxi Cab Commission, 1990-1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Tenant Assistence Program, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Tyler elementary School, 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - UDC [1/2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - UDC [2/2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - UDC, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - UDC Coop Extension Program - Ward Six Profile, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - UDC - Ross, Connie, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Union Station Bus/Parking Garage and Rail Access Facilities, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA), 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Wilson Hall School Proposal, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - WMTA, 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - WMTA, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - WMTA Board of Directors Meeting, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - WMTA - McGilvery, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Washington Gas, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Water and Sewer Utility, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Zoning Commission, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Government Business and Correspondence [1/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Government Business and Correspondence [2/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Government Business and Correspondence, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Government Business and Correspondence [1/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Government Business and Correspondence [2/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Government Business and Correspondence [1/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Government Business and Correspondence [2/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and official business of government branches of the United States and DC governments, 1985-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3
    - 10 Year Home Rule Celebration: Corr. to Community, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Democratic National Convention, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 1990 Congressional Calendar, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Issuance System, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - AFSCME - DC Government, 1985-1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Councilmember John H., 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Bills & Commissions, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Boards and Commissions, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Budget Cuts, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Candidates for Public Office, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Castillo, Mario, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Civil Complaint Violation NPDES, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - David Clarke - Chairman of Council [1/3], 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - David Clarke - Chairman of Council [2/3], 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - David Clarke - Chairman of Council [3/3], 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Commission on Domestic Partnerships for Government Employees - 1990 Questionnaire, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Commission on Latino Community Development, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Commission on Public Health, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Committee of Appropriations, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Committe of Finance and Revenue, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Committe on Housing and Economic Development, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Public Services, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Public Services - Budget, 1990-1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Matters, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Consumer and Regulating Affairs (NPW's letters to the Dept.) [1/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Consumer and Regulatory Affairs (NPW's letters to the Dept.) [2/2], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Correctional Treatment Facility Advisory Committee, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Council of the District of Columbia Calendar of the Week, May 10, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Council of DC - Shadow Delegates, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Council of Governments - Committees, Budgets, 1986-1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Canal of Government Meetings, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Council Innauguration, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Council Period 8 COW and Legislative 1990 Schedule & Committee Schedule, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Councilman Otis L. Hayward, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Councilman HR Crawford, 1987-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - David A. Clarke, et al vs. United States of America [1/2], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - David A. Clarke, et al vs. United States of America [2/2], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Treasury, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Deputy Mayor for Economic Development, 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - DC Annual Cleanup/Fix Up, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Bicentennial Commission, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - DC Board of Elections & Ethics, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - D.C. City Council Retreat 1989, Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - DC Commission for Women, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - D.C. Courthouse, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - D.C. Help Calls, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Inaugural Planning Committee, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - DC Courts - Larry Polonsky, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - DC Democratic State Committee, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - D.C. Employees One Fund Drive, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - DC National Guard, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - DC Prison Task Force, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - DC Statehood, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - DC Statehood Compact Commission [1/2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - DC Statehood Compact Commission [2/2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - DC Statehood Constitutional Convention Initiative of 1979 Amend Act, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - DC Statehood Party, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - DC Superior Court, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - DC Superior Court - Sentencing Guidelines, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - DC Zoning Commission, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Democratic State Committee, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Public Works, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Deputy Mayor for Finance, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - District Council Journal, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia, Election Polling Places, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - District Personnel Insurance System, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Domestic Partnership Commission, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Drug Enforcement Administration, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - DC Help Calls, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Embassy of India, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Emergency Medicine Advisory Committee, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Enterprise Zone Study Commission, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Evans, Daniel, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Congressman Walter Fauntroy, 1984-1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 15)